<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources | Yujia Peng PKU</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Resources</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Artificial Intelligence Picture System (SAIPS)  ​​</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024saips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024saips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Artificial Intelligence Picture System (SAIPS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction:&lt;/strong&gt; We developed the Social Artificial Intelligence Picture System (SAIPS), based on a generative multimodal artificial intelligence model. The system contains 279 social scenario images and 118 control images, generated using AI tools such as Stable Diffusion-XL and DALL-E 2. The pictures were generated along three theoretical dimensions grounded in existing theories related to social anxiety:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emotional Expression:&lt;/strong&gt; Pictures depict emotional expressions categorized as negative, neutral, or positive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Dominance:&lt;/strong&gt; Pictures include scenarios with a dominant individual (i.e., one agent presenting a sense of being more important or stronger than other agents in the picture, or than the observer) or otherwise (e.g., peer-like relationships, or a single agent).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eye Contact:&lt;/strong&gt; Some pictures involve direct eye contact between characters and the observer, while others do not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All pictures were uniformly resized to 1024×768 pixels to maintain consistency across the dataset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, SAIPS includes five subjective ratings: Social Anxiety Rating (SAR), Valence, Arousal, Involvement, and Picture-Text Consistency. These ratings offer a more comprehensive analysis of how images influence individuals&amp;rsquo; psychological responses. The system also provides objective ratings, including image descriptions, scene characteristics, and the number of characters present, offering a multi-layered data set for research purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To explore specific response patterns to social scenarios, SAIPS includes 118 control images without people, which help enhance the system&amp;rsquo;s accuracy in predicting social anxiety traits. SAIPS serves as a valuable resource for research on social anxiety, mental health, and the development of AI-based diagnostic and therapeutic tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Citation:&lt;/strong&gt; Ju, Q., Xu, Z., Chen, Z., Fan, J., Zhang, H., &amp;amp; Peng, Y. (2025). Screening Social Anxiety with the Social Artificial Intelligence Picture System. Journal of Anxiety Disorders, 109, 102955. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.janxdis.2024.102955&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.janxdis.2024.102955&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agreement:&lt;/strong&gt; Researchers requesting access to the SAIPS database must sign the SAIPS Release Agreement. Please review the agreement details below. After signing, send a scanned copy to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:junoq0420@163.com&#34;&gt;junoq0420@163.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:yujia_peng@pku.edu.cn&#34;&gt;yujia_peng@pku.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt; with the subject line “SAIPS request.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/yjpeng11/yjpeng11.github.io/refs/heads/main/resources/2024saips/Agreement-SAIPS-PKU-JU-PENG-2024.pdf&#34; download=&#34;Agreement-SAIPS-PKU-JU-PENG-2024.pdf&#34;&gt;Download the SAIPS Release Agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms and Conditions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For Academic Use Only:&lt;/strong&gt; The SAIPS dataset is strictly for academic and research purposes and must not be used for commercial purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publication Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Any paper or report using SAIPS images must include the citation of the article mentioned above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Redistribution or Modification:&lt;/strong&gt; Redistribution, publication, copying, or modification of the SAIPS dataset is prohibited without prior written approval from the SAIPS Principal Investigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recommended reading list, papers, books  ​​</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024recommend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024recommend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This curated selection of books and articles offers thought-provoking ideas and valuable insights across a variety of topics.
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to expand your knowledge, explore new perspectives, or simply find inspiration,
these resources are sure to enrich your understanding and spark your curiosity.This list has something for everyone.
Access the full list here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.qq.com/sheet/DUUhVcWRUa0dRcVlH?tab=BB08J2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://docs.qq.com/sheet/DUUhVcWRUa0dRcVlH?tab=BB08J2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Action Photorealistic and Point-light Videos (HAPPV)  ​​</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024cnnfmri/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2024cnnfmri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HAPPV includes photorealistic and point-light videos of 36 human actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Action stimuli used in the experiment were generated from the Carnegie Mellon University Motion Capture Database (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mocap.cs.cmu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://mocap.cs.cmu.edu&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As in (Dittrich, 1993), action categories were grouped into three semantic classes: Locomotory action (jumping, running, and walking), Instrumental action (ball bouncing, playing an instrument, and golf swing), and Social action (dancing, greeting, and showing directions)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] Yujia Peng, Xizi Gong, Hongjing Lu, Fang Fang; Human Visual Pathways for Action Recognition Versus Deep Convolutional Neural Networks: Representation Correspondence in Late But Not Early Layers. J Cogn Neurosci 2024; doi: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1162/jocn_a_02233&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1162/jocn_a_02233&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To download, please fill out this form: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/OtRRPQ9.aspx#&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/OtRRPQ9.aspx#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaire – Adults (CSAQ-A) ​​</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2023csaq-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2023csaq-a/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSAQ-A measures social anxiety traits from five dimensions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;F1. Speaking in public/talking with people in authority

F2. Interactions with the opposite sex

F3. Assertive expression of annoyance, disgust, or displeasure

F4. Criticism and embarrassment

F5. Interactions with strangers
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Objective: To test the validity and reliability of the Chinese version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaires-Adults (CSAQ-A).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Methods: Totally 555 participants [aged 18 to 60 years, average age (29 ± 8) years old] were recruited to complete the CSAQ-A. The Liebowitz Social Anxiety Scale (LSAS), the Brief Fear of Negative Evaluation Scale (BFNE) and several questionnaires related to anxiety and depression were conducted to test the criterion validity. After 4 weeks,143 subjects were retested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Results: Confirmatory factor analysis demonstrated that the five-dimensional structure of the CSAQ-A exhibited excellent fit indices. The CSAQ-A scores showed positive correlations with the LSAS, BFNE and other measurements of anxiety and depression (ICC=0.395-0.668, Ps&amp;lt;0.001). The internal consistency of the scale was high (Cronbach&amp;rsquo;s alpha = 0.96), and the test-retest reliability was acceptable (0.80).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Chinese version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaire-Adults has good validity and reliability and can effectively evaluate social anxiety in the Chinese adult population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] 王愉茜，臧寅垠，彭玉佳. 中文版成人社交焦虑量表的信效度检验[J].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[2] Caballo VE, Salazar IC, Irurtia MJ, et al. The multidimensional nature and multicultural validity of a new measure of social anxiety: The Social Anxiety Questionnaire for Adults[J]. Behav Ther. 2012;43(2):313-328. doi: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.beth.2011.07.001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.beth.2011.07.001&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To download, please fill out this form: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/mqAThSP.aspx#&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/mqAThSP.aspx#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
