<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources | Yujia Peng PKU</title>
    <link>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Resources</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://yjpeng11.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Action Photorealistic and Point-light Videos (HAPPV)  ​​</title>
      <link>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/2024cnnfmri/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/2024cnnfmri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HAPPV includes photorealistic and point-light videos of 36 human actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Action stimuli used in the experiment were generated from the Carnegie Mellon University Motion Capture Database (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mocap.cs.cmu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://mocap.cs.cmu.edu&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As in (Dittrich, 1993), action categories were grouped into three semantic classes: Locomotory action (jumping, running, and walking), Instrumental action (ball bouncing, playing an instrument, and golf swing), and Social action (dancing, greeting, and showing directions)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] Yujia Peng, Xizi Gong, Hongjing Lu, Fang Fang; Human Visual Pathways for Action Recognition Versus Deep Convolutional Neural Networks: Representation Correspondence in Late But Not Early Layers. J Cogn Neurosci 2024; doi: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1162/jocn_a_02233&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1162/jocn_a_02233&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To download, please fill out this form: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/OtRRPQ9.aspx#&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/OtRRPQ9.aspx#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaire – Adults (CSAQ-A) ​​</title>
      <link>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/2023csaq-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yjpeng11.github.io/resources/2023csaq-a/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSAQ-A measures social anxiety traits from five dimensions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;F1. Speaking in public/talking with people in authority

F2. Interactions with the opposite sex

F3. Assertive expression of annoyance, disgust, or displeasure

F4. Criticism and embarrassment

F5. Interactions with strangers
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Objective: To test the validity and reliability of the Chinese version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaires-Adults (CSAQ-A).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Methods: Totally 555 participants [aged 18 to 60 years, average age (29 ± 8) years old] were recruited to complete the CSAQ-A. The Liebowitz Social Anxiety Scale (LSAS), the Brief Fear of Negative Evaluation Scale (BFNE) and several questionnaires related to anxiety and depression were conducted to test the criterion validity. After 4 weeks,143 subjects were retested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Results: Confirmatory factor analysis demonstrated that the five-dimensional structure of the CSAQ-A exhibited excellent fit indices. The CSAQ-A scores showed positive correlations with the LSAS, BFNE and other measurements of anxiety and depression (ICC=0.395-0.668, Ps&amp;lt;0.001). The internal consistency of the scale was high (Cronbach&amp;rsquo;s alpha = 0.96), and the test-retest reliability was acceptable (0.80).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Chinese version of the Social Anxiety Questionnaire-Adults has good validity and reliability and can effectively evaluate social anxiety in the Chinese adult population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] 王愉茜，臧寅垠，彭玉佳. 中文版成人社交焦虑量表的信效度检验[J].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[2] Caballo VE, Salazar IC, Irurtia MJ, et al. The multidimensional nature and multicultural validity of a new measure of social anxiety: The Social Anxiety Questionnaire for Adults[J]. Behav Ther. 2012;43(2):313-328. doi: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.beth.2011.07.001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.beth.2011.07.001&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To download, please fill out this form: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/mqAThSP.aspx#&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.wjx.cn/vm/mqAThSP.aspx#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
